Too ghoul for school.
Halloweentown High is a adventure, comedy, family
film directed by Mark A.Z. Dippé.
Marnie puts her magic on the line to get several Halloweentown
teenagers transferred to her high school in the mortal world.
But soon, Marnie and her new friends are in trouble and out of luck
when the evil Knight Of The Iron Dagger appears.
He's determined to destroy all things magical, and it's up to Marnie to
save her high school, the human world and her magic.
Marnie Piper, played by Kimberly J. Brown.
Agatha 'Aggie' Cromwell, played by Debbie Reynolds.
Gwen Cromwell Piper, played by Judith Hoag.
Sophie Piper Cromwell, played by Emily Roeske.
Ethan Dalloway, played by Lucas Grabeel.
Dylan Piper Cromwell, played by Joey Zimmerman.
Halloweentown is an American television series of four fantasy films released as Disney Channel Original Movies: Halloweentown
(1998), Halloweentown II: Kalabar's Revenge (2001), Halloweentown High (2004), and Return to Halloweentown (2006).
The film explores themes of witch, magic, holiday, halloween, sorcery.
The tone is lighthearted.